[{"answer": " Hello", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Hi, Juan.  Its me, Carlos", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Hello", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Carlos.  How are you", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Hi, Juan.  Its me, Carlos", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Im doing good.  How about you", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Carlos.  How are you", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Pretty good.  I have exams this week, so its been kind of hectic", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Im doing good.  How about you", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Do you like your classes", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Pretty good.  I have exams this week, so its been kind of hectic", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " For the most part, yeah.  Ones a real snoozer, but the rest are good", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Do you like your classes", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " So, Ive decided that Im definitely going to try to go to a university in the U.S", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 21, "question": " For the most part, yeah.  Ones a real snoozer, but the rest are good", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Thats great!  I know you will really like it", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 25, "question": " So, Ive decided that Im definitely going to try to go to a university in the U.S", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Can I ask you a question", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Thats great!  I know you will really like it", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Can I ask you a question", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Ive been reading a lot on the web about the I-20.  I have no clue what this is", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Sure.  Its a really important immigration document for F-1 students", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Ive been reading a lot on the web about the I-20.  I have no clue what this is", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Does the embassy give it to you", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Sure.  Its a really important immigration document for F-1 students", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " No, the schools that you get accepted to issue it to you", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Does the embassy give it to you", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Oh, I didnt know that.  Well, whats it for", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 38, "question": " No, the schools that you get accepted to issue it to you", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " The first thing you use it for is to apply for your F-1 visa.  Its part of th", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Oh, I didnt know that.  Well, whats it for", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Do we need it after that", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 43, "question": " The first thing you use it for is to apply for your F-1 visa.  Its part of th", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Yes, you have to keep it the entire time youre a student in the U.S", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Do we need it after that", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " What kind of information is on it", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Yes, you have to keep it the entire time youre a student in the U.S", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " It has your name, date of birth, country of birth and citizenship, the school wher", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 46, "question": " What kind of information is on it", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " So, a lot of stuff", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 50, "question": " It has your name, date of birth, country of birth and citizenship, the school wher", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Yes, its one of the documents that shows what you are doing in the U.S.  It ha", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 51, "question": " So, a lot of stuff", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Can I extend it", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Yes, its one of the documents that shows what you are doing in the U.S.  It ha", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Yeah, if youre not going to graduate by the end date on your I-20, you have t", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Can I extend it", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Got it.  Ill have to keep an eye on it", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Yeah, if youre not going to graduate by the end date on your I-20, you have t", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Thats the most important thing to remember", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Got it.  Ill have to keep an eye on it", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Do you use it for anything else", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Thats the most important thing to remember", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Well, if you get authorization to work off-campus then that will be noted on your I", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Do you use it for anything else", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Theres a lot to remember", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Well, if you get authorization to work off-campus then that will be noted on your I", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " I know.  But, theyll go over everything once you arrive at the university at th", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Theres a lot to remember", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": "Will I be in trouble if I lose the I-20", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 76, "question": " I know.  But, theyll go over everything once you arrive at the university at th", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " No, you wont be in trouble.  But, you will have to get your international studen", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Will I be in trouble if I lose the I-20", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Im glad I have you to talk to, Juan.  Theres a lot to think about if I want t", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 82, "question": " No, you wont be in trouble.  But, you will have to get your international studen", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " No problem.  Youll become familiar with it all soon enough", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Im glad I have you to talk to, Juan.  Theres a lot to think about if I want t", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " OK.  Thanks again.  Id better let you go study", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 87, "question": " No problem.  Youll become familiar with it all soon enough", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " OK.  Talk to you soon", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 88, "question": " OK.  Thanks again.  Id better let you go study", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 89, "question": " OK.  Talk to you soon", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "04-09", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Bye", "qSentId": 89}]
